{
  "Title": "Round 4: Album art! Guess the artist, album title and which year the album was released. 1 point for each.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "The Beatles - Abbey Road (1969)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/6dGnYIeXmHdcikdzNNDMm2?si=0055c9b25d7745a3",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Nirvana - Nevermind (1991)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/2RsAajgo0g7bMCHxwH3Sk0?si=c94e24dfafc949d7",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Pink Floyd - The Dark Side of the Moon (1973)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/7Gx2q0ueNwvDp2BOZYGCMO?si=92d328608f6e48ce",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Joy Division - Unknown Pleasures (1979)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/2OPmhk5vO4qiYE4LEAC9hs?si=37d2c129d73f4c53",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Bruce Springsteen - Born in the USA (1984)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/3PzsbWSQdLCKDLxn7YZfkM?si=416afa3de5c144d1",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Green Day - Dookie (1994)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/6L89mwZXSOwYl76YXfX13s?si=7fd1349079944f37",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Taylor Swift - 1989 (2014)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/1u8c2t2Cy7UBoG4ArRcF5g?si=8fa1d96bfd974c39",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Adele - 21 (2011)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/3di5hcvxxciiqwMH1jarhY?si=ba44007fe0b94d22",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Imagine Dragons - Evolve (2017)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/1zB4vmk8tFRmM9UULNzbLB?si=766b3617ddf3468f",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Lady Gaga - The Fame Monster (2009)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/0SiywuOBRcynK0uKGWdCnn?si=db4ba89fb5d447c2",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 60000
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
